BU Records: Rufus B. Spain, Inclusive: 1960-2012, undated, Bulk: 2002-2011
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
BU Records: Rufus B. Spain
Inclusive: 1960-2012, undated, Bulk: 2002-2011
Baylor University, The Texas Collection http://www.baylor.edu/lib/texas/
BU/379
Spain, Rufus B., 1923 -
14 document boxes.
This collection contains a variety of Baylor University-related materials collected and produced by Dr. Rufus B. Spain, an educator and religious historian who served as a full-time professor in Baylor’s Department of History between 1957 and 1988, as a part-time professor between 1988 and 1998, and as the Director of the Baylor Retired Professors/Administrators Program between 1998 and 2013.
Administrative Information
Physical Description
General condition: Good.
Biography/Profile
Dr. Rufus B. Spain was born in Pickens County, Alabama, in 1923. A Baptist and a historian of Baptists, he began his higher education at two Baptist institutions in Mississippi: Clarke Junior College and Mississippi College. Spain’s time at the latter was interrupted by World War II, in which he served in Europe with the U.S. Army between 1943 and 1945. Spain finished his A.B. at Mississippi College in 1947, and he spent subsequent years gradually earning his M.A. (1948) and Ph.D. (1961), both in history, from Vanderbilt University. Along the way, Spain taught at the secondary level, served as history professor at Tennessee’s Cumberland University, and served an additional three years in the U.S. Army.
Spain came to Baylor University from Vanderbilt in 1957 and began teaching courses in the Department of History. These included American history surveys and a specialized course on American religious history. Spain’s revised Ph.D. dissertation--At Ease in Zion: A Social History of Southern Baptists, 1865-1900--was published by Vanderbilt University Press in 1967 and played a significant role in the development of the field of Southern religious history. Spain retired from full-time teaching in 1988 but taught part-time in the Department of History for another ten years. After his full retirement from teaching in 1998, Spain took on the directorship of the Baylor Retired Professors/Administrators Program, which he continued to lead until 2013. Spain spent a total of fifty-five years as an employee at Baylor University.
Scope and Content
This collection contains a variety of printed materials collected and produced by Dr. Rufus B. Spain over the course of his lengthy career at Baylor University. The earliest materials date to 1960 and the latest to 2012, but the bulk of the collection ranges between 2002 and 2012. Taken together, these materials both reflect Spain’s personal role in the Department of History and provide a window into broader events in Baylor’s history, particularly the implementation of and responses to the Baylor 2012 strategic plan. The materials are in good condition.
The first series, Series I. Active Faculty Files, reflects Rufus Spain’s tenure as a full- and part-time professor at Baylor, and covers the 1960s to the 1990s. The yearly files in this series primarily consist of administrative documents and correspondence related to the Department of History. This series also includes a number of obscure or independent student newspapers, including the NoZe Brotherhood’s The Rope and protest-oriented Vietnam War-era publications; chapel and Focus Week schedules; lecture- and conference-related materials; and newsletters from Texas politicians in state and federal office.
The final three series are, in contrast, products of Rufus Spain’s later “retirement” (but effectively part-time work with Baylor retirees). Correspondingly, the final series, Series IV. Retirement: Literary Productions, contains often-annotated newsletters of the Retired Professors/Administrators Program (RPAP). Most materials in these latter series, however, actually relate to larger topics in the life of Baylor University, particularly the presidencies of Robert Sloan, John Lilley, and Kenneth Starr, and common responses to the implementation of the Baylor 2012 strategic plan. The second series, Series II. Retirement: Correspondence, largely consists of printed email correspondence and internet articles related to Baylor 2012. The third series, Series III. Retirement: Subject Files, contains subject files largely relating to the same topic yet with particular emphases on theological conflicts and clashing institutional visions within Baylor University. Series IV, in addition to RPAP newsletters, also contains a small number of newspaper clippings and newsletters relating to Baylor 2012. (In most cases, clipped articles previously preserved in this collection have been replaced by indices and can instead be referenced in the Texas Collection's newspaper holdings.) It should be noted that these materials rarely reflect Spain’s own views and instead document a broad spectrum of perspectives on Baylor’s future, though most reflect the orientation of those who opposed the implementation of Baylor 2012.
Arrangement
Prior to current processing, this collection was housed in folders with titles and with minimal consistent organization. There were five apparent sorts of files. There were yearly files from Rufus Spain’s time as an active history professor and folders of Retired Professors/Administrators Program newsletters--these were the only materials organized consistently--as well as files of correspondence, newspaper clippings, and subject-based materials from Spain’s later years of semi-retirement. There was a previous inventory of the materials from those later years.
In the course of processing, the collection was refoldered and the folders were titled to reflect the types of materials found within. Folders of similar materials were grouped together and then organized either chronologically (as in the case of the yearly files, correspondence, clippings, and newsletters) or alphabetically (as in the case of the subject files). Additionally, clippings and newsletters were grouped into the same series and folders were alphabetized within that series. The internal order of the folders has been maintained.
Currently, the collection contains four series: I. Active Faculty Files, II. Retirement Correspondence, III. Retirement Subject Files, and IV. Retirement Literary Productions.
Access Restrictions
All requests for copying of materials must be submitted to The Texas Collection in writing. Please use the Request Form for Copying Materials sheet. Unpublished materials authored or otherwise produced by the creator (s) of this collection are in the public domain. There are no restrictions on use. Copyright status for other collection materials is unknown. Transmission or reproduction of materials protected by U.S. Copyright Law (Title 17, U.S.C.) beyond that allowed by fair use requires the written permission of the copyright owners. Works not in the public domain cannot be commercially exploited without permission of the copyright owners. Responsibility for any use rests exclusively with the user. Restricted until 2037-01-01.
Acquisition Information
Accession No. BU/379. Acquired 2013-02-12
Related Resources
Related collection materials
In addition to this collection, The Texas Collection maintains an oral history conducted with Rufus Spain in 1987: Spain (Rufus B) Oral Memoirs (Accession #2828).
Related references
Hunt, Alan. “Dr. Rufus Spain to Head BU Retired Faculty Program.” Media Communications, Baylor University. 1998 September 22.
“Retired Professors/Administrators Program Honors Rufus Spain and Welcomes New Director.” BaylorNews Online, Baylor University. 2013 January 25.
Spain, Rufus B. “Vita.” BU Records: Rufus B. Spain, Accession #BU/379, Box #1, Folder #9, The Texas Collection, Baylor University.
Index Terms
Subjects (Organizations)
Baylor University -- Faculty.; Baylor University -- History -- 20th century.
Subjects
Church controversies -- Baptists -- History -- 20th century.
Genres
Business correspondence.; Calendars.; Clippings (Books, newspapers, etc.); Conference materials.; Newsletters.; Newspapers.
- Active Faculty Files, Inclusive: 1960-1992, undated, Bulk: 1960-1970; 1
  Administrative Information
  Physical Description
  General condition: Good.
  Biography/Profile
  This series reflects Rufus Spain’s tenure as a full- and part-time professor at Baylor from 1957 to 1998. It consists of administrative documents, correspondence, student publications, programs from campus events such as guest lectures and Focus Weeks, and political advertisements and newsletters. This series is in good condition.
  - Correspondence, Pamphlets, Printed Materials, and Reports, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Clippings, Pamphlets, Printed Materials, and Reports (1961) (1 of 2), 1960-1961 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Clippings, Pamphlets, Printed Materials, and Reports (1961) (2 of 2), 1960-1961 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Clippings, Newsletters, Pamphlets, and Reports (1962) (1 of 2), 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Clippings, Newsletters, Pamphlets, and Reports (1962) (2 of 2), 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, Correspondence, Newsletters, Pamphlets, and Reports (1 of 2), 1963 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, Correspondence, Newsletters, Pamphlets, and Reports (2 of 2), 1963 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, Correspondence, Newsletters, Pamphlets, and Printed Materials (1 of 2), 1964 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Clippings, Correspondence, Newsletters, Pamphlets, and Printed Materials (2 of 2), 1964 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, Newsletters, Pamphlets, Printed Materials, and Reports (1965) (1 of 2), 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, Newsletters, Pamphlets, Printed Materials, and Reports (1965) (2 of 2), 1964-1965 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Newsletters, Pamphlets, Printed Materials, and Reports, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, Correspondence, Newsletters, Pamphlets, and Reports (1967), 1965-1967 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Newsletters, Pamphlets, Printed Materials, and Statements (1968), 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Articles, Correspondence, Newsletters, Pamphlets, and Printed Materials (1969), 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Newsletters, Pamphlets, and Printed Materials, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Magazine and Memoranda, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, Newsletters, Pamphlets, Press Release, and Printed Materials, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Clippings, Memoranda, Newsletters, Printed Materials, and Reports, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Desk Calendar, Memoranda, Newsletter, Pamphlet, and Printed Materials, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Clippings, Correspondence, Desk Calendar, Newsletters, and Printed Materials (1981), 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, Desk Calendar, Memoranda, and Printed Materials (1982), 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Clippings, Correspondence, Desk Calendar, Memorandum, and Printed Materials, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Desk Calendar, Newsletters, and Printed Materials, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, Desk Calendar, Newsletter, Promotional Materials, and Printed Materials (1985), 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Clippings and Desk Calendar, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, Correspondence, Memoranda, Pamphlets, and Printed Materials (1987), 1984-1987 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, Correspondence, Desk Calendar, Promotional Materials, and Printed Materials, 1988, undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Clippings and Desk Calendar, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Clipping and Desk Calendar (1990), 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Clippings, Desk Calendar, and Memorandum (1991), 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Clippings, Desk Calendar, and Printed Materials (1992), 1991-1992, undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Student Academic Records [RESTRICTED], 1962-1963 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Articles and Clippings: Indices, 1961-1988 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Retirement Correspondence, Inclusive: 1991-2012, undated, Bulk: 2002-2010; 2
  This series is a product of Rufus Spain’s semi-retirement as the director of the Baylor Retired Professors/Administrators Program, a position he held between 1998 and 2012. It consists primarily of printed email correspondence and other materials relating to the Baylor 2012 strategic plan, as it evolved under the presidencies of Robert Sloan, John Lilley, and Kenneth Starr. This series is in good condition.
  - Correspondence (1 of 2), 2002 May-2003 June (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence (2 of 2), 2002 May-2003 June (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence (1 of 2), 2003 July-August (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence (2 of 2), 2003 July-August (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence (1 of 2), 2003 September-October (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence (2 of 2), 2003 September-October (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence (1 of 2), 2003 November-2004 January (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence (2 of 2), 2003 November-2004 January (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence (1 of 2), 2004 February-March (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence (2 of 2), 2004 February-March (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence (1 of 2), 2004 April-May (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence (2 of 2), 2004 April-May (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence (1 of 2), 2004 June-July 15 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence (2 of 2), 2004 June-July 15 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence (1 of 2), 2004 July 16-August 10 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence (2 of 2), 2004 July 16-August 10 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence (1 of 2), 2004 August 16-September 15 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence (2 of 2), 2004 August 16-September 15 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence (1 of 2), 2004 September 16-October 7 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence (2 of 2), 2004 September 16-October 7 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 2004 October 11-29 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence (2004 November), 2004 October-November (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence (2004 December), 2004 November-December (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 2005 January, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence (1 of 2), 2005 February (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence (2 of 2), 2005 February (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence (2005 March), 2005 January-March (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence (2005 April) (1 of 2), 2005 January-May (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence (2005 April) (2 of 2), 2005 January-May (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence (1 of 3), 2005 May-August (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence (2 of 3), 2005 May-August (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence (3 of 3), 2005 May-August (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence (1 of 2), 2005 September-October (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence (2 of 2), 2005 September-October (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence (1 of 2), 2005 November-December, undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence (2 of 2), 2005 November-December, undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence (1 of 2), 2006 January-March (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence (2 of 2), 2006 January-March (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence (1 of 2), 2006 April-June (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence (2 of 2), 2006 April-June (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence (1 of 2), 2006 July-August (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence (2 of 2), 2006 July-August (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence (1 of 2), 2006 September-December (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence (2 of 2), 2006 September-December (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence (1 of 2), 2007 January-April, undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence (2 of 2), 2007 January-April, undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence (1 of 2), 2007 May-July, undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence (2 of 2), 2007 May-July, undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence (2007 August-September) (1 of 2), 2007 July-September (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence (2007 August-September) (2 of 2), 2007 July-September (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence (2007 October-2008 March), 2007 October-2008 April (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 2008 April-May (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence (2008 June-July) (1 of 2), 2008 June-August (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence (2008 June-July) (2 of 2), 2008 June-August (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence (1 of 2), 2008 August-October (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence (2 of 2), 2008 August-October (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence (2008 December-2009 June) (1 of 3), 2008 November-2009 June (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence (2008 December-2009 June) (2 of 3), 2008 November-2009 June (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence (2008 December-2009 June) (3 of 3), 2008 November-2009 June (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence (2008 July-September) (1 of 2), 2008 August-2009 September (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence (2008 July-September) (2 of 2), 2008 August-2009 September (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence (2009 October) (1 of 2), 2009 September-November) (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence (2009 October) (2 of 2), 2009 September-November) (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence (2009 November-December), 2009 October-December (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence (1 of 3), 2010 January-February (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence (2 of 3), 2010 January-February (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence (3 of 3), 2010 January-February (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence (2010 March-May) (1 of 2), 2010 February-October (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence (2010 March-May) (2 of 2), 2010 February-October (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence (1 of 2), 2010 June-December (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence (2 of 2), 2010 June-December (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence (2011 January-May) (1 of 2), 2010 December-2011 May (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence (2011 January-May) (2 of 2), 2010 December-2011 May (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence (2011 June-December) (1 of 2), 2011 February-December (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence (2011 June-December) (2 of 2), 2011 February-December (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence (2012), 2011 December-2012 November (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence (1 of 2), 1991-2004, undated (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence (2 of 2), 1991-2004, undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Retirement: Subject Files, Inclusive: 1986-2007, undated, Bulk: 2002-2005; 3
  Like Series II, this series contains materials reflective of Rufus Spain’s retirement years. The subject files in this series highlight responses from across the Baylor community to particular facets of the Baylor 2012 strategic plan as proposed by President Robert B. Sloan, Jr., including the relationship of faith to higher education and the priority of graduate as opposed to undergraduate education. This series is in good condition.
  - Baylor Alumni Association/Board of Regents Controversy: Addresses, Alumni Survey, Articles, Clippings, and Correspondence, 2007 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Baylor Alumni Association/Board of Regents Controversy: Articles, Clippings, Correspondence, Printed Materials, and Reports, 2007 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Baylor University Retirees and the Regent Presidential Search Committee: Correspondence and Printed Materials (2005 April 19), 2002-2005 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Christianity and the Soul of the University: Conference Materials: Baylor University (2004 March 25-27) (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Colloquy in Honor of Donald D. Schmeltekopf: Correspondence, Essays, and Printed Materials (2003 April 10-11) (1 of 2), 1986-2003 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Colloquy in Honor of Donald D. Schmeltekopf: Correspondence, Essays, and Printed Materials (2003 April 10-11) (2 of 2), 1986-2003 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - “Connections”: Professors Associated with Baylor University: Articles, Correspondence, and Printed Materials, 2001-2005 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - CRIB (Committee to Restore Integrity to Baylor): Administrative Materials and Treatise, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Referendum on Robert B. Sloan: Articles, Correspondence, and Report, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Survey: Baylor University Office of Work/Life Programs: Correspondence, Findings Reports, and Printed Materials, 2003, undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Survey and Findings Report: Baylor University Office of Work/Life Programs, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Faith and Learning: Baylor University: Articles, Clippings, Correspondence, and Printed Materials (1 of 2), 1991-2004 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Faith and Learning: Baylor University: Articles, Clippings, Correspondence, and Printed Materials (2 of 2), 1991-2004 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Gilbreath, Kent: Clippings, Correspondence, and Essays, 1993-2003, undated (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Gilbreath, Kent: Essays and Relevant Correspondence, 2005, undated (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Henry, Douglas V.: Paper: “Can Baptist Theology Sustain the Life of the Mind?”, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Jeffrey-Wheaton Speech Controversy: Address, Memoranda, and Notes (1 of 2), 2004, undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Jeffrey-Wheaton Speech Controversy: Address, Memoranda, and Notes (2 of 2), 2004, undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Letter of Affirmation of William Underwood: Addresses, Correspondence, and Printed Materials (1 of 2), 2005 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Letter of Affirmation of William Underwood: Addresses, Correspondence, and Printed Materials (2 of 2), 2005 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Letter of Affirmation of William Underwood: Certified Mail Receipts, 2005 October (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Letter of Affirmation of William Underwood: Correspondence and Printed Materials (1 of 3), 2005 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Letter of Affirmation of William Underwood: Correspondence and Printed Materials (2 of 3), 2005 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Letter of Affirmation of William Underwood: Correspondence and Printed Materials (3 of 3), 2005 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Michael Polanyi Center: Baylor University: Articles, Clippings, Correspondence, Press Releases, and Reports, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - “Network”: Professors and Institutions Related to Baylor University’s Great Texts, Honors, and University Scholars Programs: Printed Materials, 2003, undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - New Hires: Baylor University: Statistical Materials (1992-1995), circa 2003 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - New Hires: Baylor University: Statistical Materials (1996-1999), circa 2003 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - New Hires: Baylor University: Statistical Materials (2000-2003), circa 2003 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - New Hires: Baylor University: Statistical Materials and Correspondence, circa 2004 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Professor Teaching Loads: Baylor University: Correspondence, Printed Materials, Reports, and Statistical Materials, 2003-2004, undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Provost Search Committee: Baylor University: Essays, Printed Materials, and Reports, 2002, undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Pruit Memorial Symposia: Correspondence, Drafts, Programs, and Schedules, 2003-2005 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Reactions to John M. Lilley: Correspondence, 2005 November (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Senate Referendum Concerning Presidency of Robert Sloan: Correspondence (1 of 2), 2004 October (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Senate Referendum Concerning Presidency of Robert Sloan: Correspondence (2 of 2), 2004 October (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Teaching Loads: Baylor University: Statistical Materials, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - The Call to Justice: Conference Materials, Correspondence, and Papers: Vatican City (2005 March 16-18) (1 of 2) (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - The Call to Justice: Conference Materials, Correspondence, and Papers: Vatican City (2005 March 16-18) (2 of 2) (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - The Future of Baptist Higher Education: Conference Materials, George W. Truett Theological Seminary (2005 April 18-19) (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Vision 2012: Articles, Essays, Memorandum, and Printed Materials, 1991-2003 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Vision 2012: Correspondence and Fact Sheet, 2003, undated (Box 13, Folder 12)